forex-robot-world-cup.com 2013-07-10

# The International EA Competition

1\. Acknowledgment And Acceptance Of Terms

The International EA Competition Organization is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing http://www.InternationalEACompetition.com, you acknowledge and fully understand the International EA Competition Organization Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

2\. Participating Merchant Policies

Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in the International EA Competition Organization's services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

3\. Information We Collect And How We Use It

The owners and publishers of http://www.InternationalEACompetition.com collect certain information from and about its users in three ways - directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.

**a.** Web Server Logs

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage.

Examples of information we may track include but not limited to:

Your Internet protocol address.  
The kind of browser or computer you use.  
Number of links you click within the site.  
State or country from which you accessed the site.  
Date and time of your visit.  
Name of your Internet service provider.  
Web page you linked to our site from.  
Pages you viewed on the site.

**b.** Use of Cookies

The owners and publishers of http://www.InternationalEACompetition.com may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.

The owners and publishers of http://www.InternationalEACompetition.com reserve the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website unless there is a temporary, overriding customer value (such as merging into http://www.InternationalEACompetition.com a site that relies on third-party cookies).

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

**c.** Personal Information Users

Visitors to our website can register to purchase services. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, e-mail, telephone number or facsimile number, account number and other relevant information. If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary, including:

To fulfil your service requests for services.  
To protect ourselves from liability,  
To respond to legal process or comply with law, or  
In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

4\. Use Of Web Beacons Or GIF Files

http://www.InternationalEACompetition.com's web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons, sometimes also called single-pixel gifs, that allow the owners and publishers of http://www.InternationalEACompetition.com to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. The owners and publishers of http://www.InternationalEACompetition.com may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or e-mail communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or e-mails and compiles anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and e-mails bring you to our website and how you use the site. The owners and publishers of http://www.InternationalEACompetition.com prohibit Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.

5\. Accessing Web Account Information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by contacting our support attendants via our **Contact** page.

6\. Under The Age Of 18

The International EA Competition Organization does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under the age of 18\. If we discover we have received any information from a child under the age of 18 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe the International EA Competition Organization has any information from or about anyone under 18, please contact us at the address listed below.

7\. Changes To This Statement

The owners and publishers of http://www.InternationalEACompetition.com have the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

8\. Governing Law

This policy and the use of this Site and purchase of any product from this site are governed by the laws of Hong Kong. If a dispute arises under this Policy (agreement) we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon arbitrator in the following location: Hong Kong.

**_Company Details_**  
Reality Based Forex Limited  
BLK A, 15/F Hillier Commercial Building  
65-67 Bonham Strand East  
Sheung Wan  
Hong Kong

This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

By becoming a member of this website or using this website you agree that you unconditionally accept this disclaimer agreement.

You further agree that Reality Based Forex Limited, its Directors and representatives cannot be held liable for any loses, injury or damages the user may claim as per the laws of the Hong Kong or any other country.

9\. Contacting Us

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us via our **Contact** page. 

The views and opinions provided by The International EA Competition are not endorsed nor controlled by our preferred Forex brokers. Further, Forex brokers are not responsible for their availability, content, or delivery of services and will not accept liability for any loss or damage, including without limitation to, any loss of profit, which may arise directly or indirectly from use of or reliance on such information. 

Hypothetical performance results have many inherent limitations, some of which are described below. No representation is being made that any account will or is likely to achieve profits or losses similar to those shown. In fact, there are frequently sharp differences between hypothetical performance results and the actual results subsequently achieved by any particular trading program. One of the limitations of hypothetical performance results is that they are generally prepared with the benefit of hindsight. In addition, hypothetical trading does not involve financial risk, and no hypothetical trading record can completely account for the impact of financial risk in actual trading. For example, the ability to withstand losses or to adhere to a particular trading program in spite of trading losses are material points which can also adversely affect trading results. There are numerous other factors related to the markets in general or to the implementation of any specific trading program which cannot be fully accounted for in the preparation of hypothetical performance results and all of which can adversely affect actual trading results.

At all times you must note that you shall not and cannot assume, nor do we provide, any assurance that any prior successes, or past results, as to income earnings, can be used as an indication of your future success or results. By relying on or using any of our products, services or written materials or information, you acknowledge unequivocally, that we make no claim, nor do we make any guarantee or warrantee or representation of any kind, in terms of the correctness, accuracy, reliability, currency or otherwise thereof. The entire risk as to the results and outcome and performance of the products and services and use of any information or product or material provided by ourselves, are assumed by you.

The International EA Competition (IEAC) is neither licensed nor regulated in any country and we cannot give investment advice on any matter. If you are unsure about anything on this website, please seek independent financial advice. Your use of the website is your acceptance of our full terms and conditions located on our website and you acknowledge that you will not use the website or purchase any product from the IEAC that would require the IEAC to be registered or regulated in your country.
